<topics>
	<topic>
		<num>1</num>
		<author>Nadine Maron</author>
		<type>time-independent</type>
		<title>easy one pot pasta</title>
		<description>
			An easy recipe for a pasta dish that only requires one pot is needed.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document will provide a pasta recipe that is easy to follow and does not require many ingredients.
			It should require no more than one pot to prepare.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>2</num>
		<author>Nadine Maron</author>
		<type>explicit-time</type>
		<title>GNTM winner 2024</title>
		<description>
			Who won the GNTM final in 2024?
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document includes information about the person that won the GNTM final in 2024.
			The information should include name, age and a picture of the person.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>3</num>
		<author>Nadine Maron</author>
		<type>event</type>
		<title>hurricane Milton</title>
		<description>
			What effects did hurricane Milton have?
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document includes information about the hurricane itself, containing the date and location of its occurence.
			It should also give details about the extend of the hurricane and what area was affected the most.
			It should show what actually happened and not the predictions about the extend.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>4</num>
		<author>Nadine Maron</author>
		<type>snow cologne</type>
		<title></title>
		<description>
			When is snow supposed to fall in Cologne.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document will give a time when snow is to be expected in Cologne.
			If no specific date can be named a rough period is also accepted.
			The last time there was snow in Cologne is not relevant, only future events are relevant.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>5</num>
		<author>Nadine Maron</author>
		<type>timeliness</type>
		<title>abortion laws USA</title>
		<description>
			What are the current developments when it come to abortion laws n the USA?
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document explains the current situation in the USA, especially with the election of Donald Trump.
			It explains what plans concerning abortion laws there are and how theyy are aimed to be achieved.
			Information about the current abortion laws are also relevant.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
</topics>