<topics>
        <topic>
                <num>1</num>
                <author>Felix Zhi Yong Lin</author>
                <type>time-independent</type>
                <title>Sofa</title>
                <description>
                        How is a sofa constructed?
                </description>
                <narrative>
                        A relevant document should describe the components and construction of a sofa. 
                        It should include information about the materials used, such as the wooden frame, upholstery, fabric cover, and any mechanical features like pull-out beds. 
                        Details about durability, maintenance, and ergonomic aspects could also be valuable to provide a comprehensive understanding.</narrative>
        </topic>
        <topic>
                  <num>2</num>
                  <author>Felix Zhi Yong Lin</author>
                  <type>time-specific</type>
                  <title>StreamAwards 2024</title>
                  <description>
                          When will the StreamAwards 2024 take place?
                  </description>
                  <narrative>
                          A relevant document should not only provide the exact date and time of the event but also offer additional details. 
                          These may include the venue, the platforms on which the event will be streamed (e.g., YouTube or Twitch), and highlights such as the list of nominees or award categories. 
                          Background information about the history and significance of the event would also be helpful.</narrative>
        </topic>
        <topic>
                  <num>3</num>
                  <author>Felix Zhi Yong Lin</author>
                  <type>event</type>
                  <title>Football World Cup</title>
                  <description>
                          When and where will the next Football World Cup start?
                  </description>
                  <narrative>
                          A relevant document should provide details about the start date and venue of the next Football World Cup. 
                          Additional insights could include information about the participating teams, qualification processes, and potential favorites. 
                          Details about the stadiums, match schedules, and cultural highlights of the host country could also help to better understand the context of the event.</narrative>
          
        </topic>
        <topic>
                  <num>4</num>
                  <author>Felix Zhi Yong Lin</author>
                  <type>ambiguous</type>
                  <title>Mouse</title>
                  <description>
                          Relevant documents contain general information about the rodent "mouse."
                  </description>
                  <narrative>
                          A relevant document could describe the biology, behavior, and lifestyle of the mouse. 
                          This might include information about its diet, reproduction, natural habitats, and ecological role. 
                          Insights into its adaptations for survival, its interactions with other species, and its significance in ecological systems or as a model organism in scientific research would also be valuable. 
                          The focus is solely on the animal, not on technological devices.
                  </topic>
        <topic>
                  <num>5</num>
                  <author>Felix Zhi Yong Lin</author>
                  <type>timeliness</type>
                  <title>Current punctuality rates in German transport</title>
                  <description>
                          The query aims to find out how punctual regional trains in Germany have been over the past few weeks.
                  </description>
                  <narrative>
                          A relevant document should contain up-to-date statistics and reports on the punctuality of regional trains. 
                          Insights into regional variations, causes of delays, and efforts to improve reliability would be helpful. 
                          Additional data on trends or historical comparisons could provide context for evaluating the current situation. 
                          Such information is critical for transportation planners, commuters, and policymakers to assess the quality of public transport and implement improvements where necessary.
                  </narrative>
        </topic>
</topics>
