<topics>
	<topic>
		<num>1</num>
		<author>Max Wollenberg</author>
		<type>time-independent</type>
		<title>system hardening</title>
		<description>
			How do to secure a system against external cyberattacks?
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document will provide areas of a systems security which can be checked. 
			Additionally it should provide further assistance on how to improve on cyber resiliance if the security level falls short.
			It should not include only a short mentioning of a possible area to improve on system hardening.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>2</num>
		<author>Max Wollenberg</author>
		<type>explicit-time</type>
		<title>specs Fireblade 2020</title>
		<description>
			What are the specifics of the motorcycle of exactly this year.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document would include information about the specific information of this machine.
			This explicitly includes top speed, horsepower(hp)/kilowatt(kW), mileage (f.e. fuel l/100km), (others are optional).
			Not included are only specifics how the motorcycle feels when driving it, 
			but they can show up next to the specifics as they mostly come in pairs when appearing
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>3</num>
		<author>Max Wollenberg</author>
		<type>event</type>
		<title>Banana republic history</title>
		<description>
			How did Chiquita's exploit developing countries in their company history?
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document consists of Chiquitas (or United Fruit Company/UFC/UFOC) past how they usurped developing countries with the help of the us government or the cia.
			It should additionaly highlight the economical inhibition of the self development of the affected countries.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>4</num>
		<author>Max Wollenberg</author>
		<type>ambiguous</type>
		<title>psyops society</title>
		<description>
			How are current societies disrupted by techniques and tools from foreign countries or internal factions.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document is a article which highlights in a neutral and fact based tone what kind of tools are used and how they influence a society of an affected country.
			It should highlight what psychological tricks are used against the affected society and how the society changes because of the disruption.
			It can include examples how countries are using this technique.
			It should not include assumptions and non accredited sources. 
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>5</num>
		<author>Max Wollenberg</author>
		<type>timeliness</type>
		<title>fine too fast</title>
		<description>
			What fines and punishment exist right now for driving too fast inside the country.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document showcases recent fines for different excessive speeding inside the country.
			It also highlights the relevant punishments additional to monetary fines (f.e. license suspension, others...).
			The focus has to lie on the current fines and punishments.
			The focus should not lie on another topic. (fe. short mentioning of fines/punishments inside an newspaper, an article)
		</narrative>
	</topic>
</topics>
