<topics>
	<topic>
		<num>1</num>
	        <author>Andreas Large</author>
	        <type>time-independent</type>
            	<title>plate tectonics</title>
            	<description>
            		What is the theory of plate tectonics and how does it shape the Earth's surface?
            	</description>
            	<narrative>
                  	A relevant document should explain the theory of plate tectonics, 
			focusing on the movement of Earth's lithospheric plates and their role in earthquakes, volcanic activity, and mountain formation.
            	</narrative>
      	</topic>
      	<topic>
            	<num>2</num>
            	<author>Andreas Large</author>
            	<type>explicit-time</type>
            	<title>game awards winners 2024</title>
            	<description>
		        Information on the winners and major awards from the most important video game award ceremonies of the year 2024.            		
                </description>
            	<narrative>
			Relevant documents contain specific information about the "winners of the video game awards 2024", 
			including the "best games of the year" and major categories such as "best performance", "game of the year", "best graphics", and more. 
			The search results are expected to also include up-to-date information about the nominees and award events that are announced throughout the year. 
			This will include details about the events, winners, and award announcements that can evolve over the course of 2024.
            	</narrative>
      	</topic>
      	<topic>
            	<num>3</num>
            	<author>Andreas Large</author>
            	<type>event</type>
            	<title>super bowl security measures</title>
            	<description>
            		Information about the security measures implemented for the Super Bowl, including access controls,
                        surveillance, and emergency management protocols.
            	</description>
            	<narrative>
                        Relevant documents will include up-to-date information about security measures for the Super Bowl. 
                        This may cover aspects like security checks at entrances, new surveillance technologies, the use of drones or security personnel, 
                        and potential changes due to evolving threats or societal developments.            		
                </narrative>
      	</topic>
      	<topic>
            	<num>4</num>
            	<author>Andreas Large</author>
            	<type>ambiguous</type>
            	<title>fly</title>
            	<description>
            		The query seeks information about the insect "fly," including its biology and role in the ecosystem.
            	</description>
            	<narrative>
                  	A relevant document would include details about flies as insects, such as their physical characteristics, habitats, and behavior. 
                        Other meanings of "Fly," such as human flight or slang, are not relevant.
                </narrative>
      	</topic>
      	<topic>
            	<num>5</num>
            	<author>Andreas Large</author>
            	<type>timeliness</type>
            	<title>upcoming elections michigan</title>
            	<description>
                	Information about upcoming elections in the state of Michigan, including details about the races,
			candidates, voting procedures, and key issues that may influence the outcomes.	
                </description>
            	<narrative>
                  	Relevant documents should focus on upcoming elections in Michigan, providing information about the scheduled races,
			the candidates running, and key policy issues at stake. 
			The search should include details on voting procedures, such as absentee or mail-in voting, early voting, and polling locations. 
			Additionally, documents should cover any significant changes in election laws or procedures for the upcoming election cycle,
			as well as potential factors influencing voter turnout.
                </narrative>
      	</topic>
</topics>
