<topics>
	<topic>
		<num>1</num>
		<author>Max Wollenberg</author>
		<type>time-independent</type>
		<title>system hardening</title>
		<description>
			How do i secure my system against external cyberattacks?
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document will provide areas of my systems security which i can check. 
			Additionally it should provide further assistance on how to improve my cyber resiliance if the security level falls short.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>2</num>
		<author>Max Wollenberg</author>
		<type>explicit-time</type>
		<title>specs Fireblade 2020</title>
		<description>
			I want to see exactly this model year for specs of the machine.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document would include information about the specific informations of this machine.
			This explicitly includes top speed, acceleration 0-100kmh/0-60mph, mileage (fuel l/100km), (others are optional).
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>3</num>
		<author>Max Wollenberg</author>
		<type>implicit-time</type>
		<title>banana republic</title>
		<description>
			I want to see information about Chiquita's historical exploiting developing countries.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document consists of Chiquitas past how they usurped developing countries with the help of the us government and the cia.
			It should additionaly highlight the inhibition of the self development of the affected countries.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>4</num>
		<author>Max Wollenberg</author>
		<type>ambiguous</type>
		<title>psyops</title>
		<description>
			I want to see informations about the tools used to disrupt social unity in countries.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document highlights in a neutral and fact based tone what kind of tools are used and how they affect the social life of the affected countries.
			In addition it also highlights the psychological impact on the civilians.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>5</num>
		<author>Max Wollenberg</author>
		<type>timeliness</type>
		<title>fine too fast</title>
		<description>
			I've been driven too fast! I want to know what i have to pay or how the country is going to punish me.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document showcases the different fines for different excessive speeding.
			It also highlights the relevant punishments additional to monetary fines (f.e. license suspension, others...).
		</narrative>
	</topic>
</topics>