<topics>
    <topic>
        <num>1</num>
        <author>Vadims Romanovskis</author>
        <type>time-independent</type>
        <title>Grand Canyon</title>
        <description>How was the Grand Canyon formed, and what are its unique geological features?</description>
        <narrative>
            A relevant document provides information about the formation history, geological characteristics of the Grand Canyon.
            It should include specific details about its unique rock layers, erosion processes, and significance in natural history.
            General information about other canyons or unrelated tourism data is not relevant.
        </narrative>
    </topic>
    <topic>
        <num>2</num>
        <author>Vadims Romanovskis</author>
        <type>explicit-time</type>
        <title>Gamescom 2024</title>
        <description>Which new games were presented at Gamescom 2024, and which companies participated?</description>
        <narrative>
            A relevant document contains detailed information about the new games showcased and the companies that participated at Gamescom 2024.
            Reports should specify game titles, genres, release dates, and significant announcements made during the event.
            Older reports or general gaming news unrelated to Gamescom 2024 are not relevant.
        </narrative>
    </topic>
    <topic>
        <num>3</num>
        <author>Vadims Romanovskis</author>
        <type>event</type>
        <title>German Reunification</title>
        <description>What were the political and economic consequences of German reunification in 1990?</description>
        <narrative>
            A relevant document describes the political, economic, and social transformations caused by the reunification of the Federal Republic of Germany and the German Democratic Republic.
            It should cover aspects like integration challenges, economic restructuring, and policy shifts.
            Information about unrelated political events in Germany or general historical data is not relevant.
        </narrative>
    </topic>
    <topic>
        <num>4</num>
        <author>Vadims Romanovskis</author>
        <type>ambiguous</type>
        <title>Jaguar</title>
        <description>What is relevant information about Jaguar?</description>
        <narrative>
            A relevant document should discuss recent vehicle releases, technical specifications, company news, or innovations in automobile design.
            For example, an article about the latest Jaguar electric car or the company's global market performance would be appropriate.
            A document that tells the history of a brand, a commercial website that sells a car of that brand or information about an animal is not relevant.
        </narrative>
    </topic>
    <topic>
        <num>5</num>
        <author>Vadims Romanovskis</author>
        <type>timeliness</type>
        <title>Euro/Dollar Exchange Rate</title>
        <description>What is the current exchange rate between the Euro and the US Dollar?</description>
        <narrative>
            A relevant document provides up-to-date information on the exchange rate between the Euro and the US Dollar.
            It may include current market trends, financial analysis, or factors influencing the rate.
            Historical data or speculative forecasts without current context are not relevant.
        </narrative>
    </topic>
</topics>
