<topics>
	<topic>
		<num>1</num>
		<author>Muhammed Coban</author>
		<type>time-independent</type>
		<title>Dark Souls 1 Lore</title>
		<description>
			The background story and worldbuilding of Dark Souls 1.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document provides an explanation of the lore in Dark Souls 1, a video game developed by FromSoftware. 
                        Dark Souls 1 is known for its unique approach to storytelling, 
			where the narrative is not presented directly but instead conveyed through cryptic item descriptions, NPC dialogue, and environmental details. 
                        The game explores themes such as the Age of Fire, the fading of light, and the cyclical nature of struggle.
                        It is important to note that Dark Souls 1 is the first game in the Dark Souls series, and while it is connected to its sequels, 
			documents that discuss lore from other games or other FromSoftware titles, like Bloodborne or Elden Ring, are not relevant. 
                        This topic focuses exclusively on the story and worldbuilding as presented in the original release of Dark Souls 1.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>2</num>
		<author>Muhammed Coban</author>
		<type>explicit-time</type>
		<title>"The College Dropout" Release</title>
		<description>
			The release date of Kanye West's debut album.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document provides the exact date when "The College Dropout" was released. 
                        This album marked Kanye West's entry into the music industry as a solo artist and is considered a significant milestone in hip-hop. 
                        Documents that speculate about the release without giving the precise date or discuss unrelated albums are not relevant.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>3</num>
		<author>Muhammed Coban</author>
		<type>event</type>
		<title>Yeezus Tour</title>
		<description>
			Kanye West's concert tour to promote his Yeezus album, known for its artistic and provocative performances.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			The Yeezus Tour was a landmark event in live music, showcasing Kanye West's bold artistic vision. 
                        Relevant documents would include articles, reviews, and analysis of the tour's performances, themes, and impact on the music industry. 
      			These might cover the visual elements, the setlist, and the cultural significance of the show.
      			Irrelevant documents would include product listings or merchandise related to the tour, as these do not provide insight into the event itself. 
      			The focus should be on discussions around the tour's influence, not on items for sale.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>4</num>
		<author>Muhammed Coban</author>
		<type>ambiguous</type>
		<title>Dragon Ball</title>
		<description>
			The franchise centered around the manga Dragon Ball.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document covers any aspect of the Dragon Ball franchise, including its manga, anime adaptations, video games, and merchandise. 
      			Dragon Ball is one of the most influential manga series, created by Akira Toriyama, and has spawned numerous adaptations and continuations. 
      			However, the ambiguity arises because a new series is currently airing, sparking renewed interest. 
      			Documents should focus on Dragon Ball and its franchise rather than unrelated topics, 
			but all parts of the franchise, including older works and the new series, are considered relevant.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
	<topic>
		<num>5</num>
		<author>Muhammed Coban</author>
		<type>recency</type>
		<title>PS5 Pro</title>
		<description>
			The new console from Sony.
		</description>
		<narrative>
			A relevant document provides detailed and accurate information about the PS5 Pro, focusing on its features, specifications, and release details. 
      			The PS5 Pro is an upgraded version of the PlayStation 5, designed to offer improved performance and enhanced graphics capabilities. 
      			Documents discussing the standard PS5 or other gaming consoles are not relevant. 
      			The focus is on providing information that highlights what is new and unique about the PS5 Pro or where you can buy one.
		</narrative>
	</topic>
</topics>
