<topics>
    <topic>
        <num>1</num>
        <author>Kristine Jonina</author>
        <type>time-independent</type>
        <title>Cologne Cathedral</title>
        <description>
            What is the cultural and historical significance of the Cologne Cathedral?
        </description>
        <narrative>
            A relevant document should contain information about the architecture, history, and cultural 
            significance of the Cologne Cathedral.
        </narrative>
    </topic>
    <topic>
        <num>2</num>
        <author>Kristine Jonina</author>
        <type>explicit-time</type>
        <title>9/11</title>
        <description>
            What were the consequences of 9/11?
        </description>
        <narrative>
            A relevant document should cover the political, social, and economic impacts of September 11. 
            Documents that do not relate to this event and its consequences are less relevant.
        </narrative>
    </topic>
    <topic>
        <num>3</num>
        <author>Kristine Jonina</author>
        <type>event</type>
        <title>Covid-19 Pandemic</title>
        <description>
            How has the COVID-19 pandemic changed the world?        
        </description>
        <narrative>
            A relevant document should summarize the economic, social, and health impacts of the COVID-19 
            pandemic worldwide. It should also address the measures taken to combat the virus and the long-term 
            changes in daily life. Documents that focus on another pandemic or only on medical details without 
            reference to societal changes are less relevant.
        </narrative>
    </topic>
    <topic>
        <num>4</num>
        <author>Kristine Jonina</author>
        <type>ambiguous</type>
        <title>traffic light problems germany</title>
        <description>
            What problems does the traffic light have in Germany?
        </description>
        <narrative>
            A relevant document provides the problems of the traffic light coalition in Germany. 
            A document is not relevant if it has no political reference
        </narrative>
    </topic>
    <topic>
        <num>5</num>
        <author>Kristine Jonina</author>
        <type>current</type>
        <title>Current Fashion Trends</title>
        <description>
            What are the current fashion trends for this season?
        </description>
        <narrative>
            A relevant document should name clothing items and combinations that are trending in the current 
            season. Trends from past seasons or years are not relevant, nor is the historical origin of these trends.
            Gender is irrelevant, the clothes can be for both women and men.
        </narrative>
    </topic>
</topics>